<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Justin Kurt Tin | 10 - Newton</title>
    <link>https://justinktn.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Justin Kurt Tin | 10 - Newton</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 03:21:28 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://justinktn.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BLOG #3: Exploring ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://justinktn.github.io/posts/2022/exploring-chatgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 03:21:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://justinktn.github.io/posts/2022/exploring-chatgpt/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;ChatGPT: Optimizing Language Models for Dialogue&amp;rdquo; - OpenAI What is ChatGPT?
The ability to predict how words will be connected in meaningful ways is what allows chatbots like ChatGPT to function. They have access to a huge vocabulary and knowledge base and are very excellent at contextual word understanding. Through the use of encyclopedic information, they may replicate speech patterns due to this.
 It can even do fun things like making a comedy routine about its status of it:   Even compose rapping lyrics:  OpenAI has admitted this, however, stating that &amp;ldquo;ChatGPT occasionally writes plausible-sounding but wrong or illogical answers&amp;rdquo; that is why we should not take its answer seriously matter, especially in professional cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLOG #2: The Climate Crisis Network</title>
      <link>https://justinktn.github.io/posts/2022/climate-crisis-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://justinktn.github.io/posts/2022/climate-crisis-network/</guid>
      <description>“You cannot heal in the same environment where you got sick.” – Anonymous Concept Web:
 Introduction:
If you don&amp;rsquo;t allow your wounds the space they need to breathe and regenerate, they won&amp;rsquo;t ever heal. Always find for the better changes rather than always using the same practice that makes you sick. Let go of the bad practices and always have the strength to remain true to ourselves.
We all fail and I do believe that trying and failing is always better than not trying at all and never be hesitant to attempt new things for the better of our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLOG #1: Einstein-inspired School</title>
      <link>https://justinktn.github.io/posts/2022/einstein-inspired_school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://justinktn.github.io/posts/2022/einstein-inspired_school/</guid>
      <description>What would be the design of the school&amp;rsquo;s curriculum?
The design of the school&amp;rsquo;s curriculum that Albert Einstein wants to be based on the story &amp;ldquo;On Education (1936)&amp;rdquo;, it should be subject-centered, learner-centered, and problem-centered because I believe that education is not about learning facts but thinking about ideas. No student would be required to study the same topics. Instead of making a student feel unintelligent because he was unable to comprehend the topic being taught by their teachers, we should encourage students to enhance their talents and creative thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
